BU Records: Continuing Education, Inclusive: 1978-2005, undated, Bulk: 1992-2005, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Nonprofit Education, 1983-2005; 2
  - Nonprofit Winter/Spring 2002 (2 of 2), 2001 December 20-2002 April 11 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Nonprofit Summer 2002 (1 of 2), 1992 April 29-2002 July 25, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Nonprofit Summer 2002 (2 of 2), 2001 October 15, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Nonprofit Fall 2002 (1 of 3), 2002 July 3-November 14, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Nonprofit Fall 2002 (2 of 3), 2002 October 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Nonprofit Fall 2002 (3 of 3), 2002 June 20-December 27, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Nonprofit Winter/Spring 2003, 1995-2003 April 24 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Nonprofit Summer 2003, 2003 April 8-July 15 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Nonprofit Fall 2003, 2003 September 12-November 19, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Nonprofit Winter/Spring 2004, 2003 November 10-2004 May 11 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Nonprofit Summer 2004, 2004 July 7-20 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Nonprofit Fall 2004, 2004 September 10-2005 April 23, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Nonprofit Winter/Spring 2005, 2004 November 8-2005 April 22, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - CooperDLGrants Accounting (1 of 3), 1998-2004 December 4 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - CooperDLGrants Accounting (2 of 3), 1999 January 31-2001 December 31 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Cooper--Grants Accounting (3 of 3), 1998 September 4-2001 January 31 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Foundation, 2004 December 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - “Fundraising” Hand-outs to Class, 1999 January 1-March 1, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Nonprofit Course Participants, 1999 January-2003 July, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Class Evaluations, 1999 February 19-2000 November 9 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Letters, 1999 April 3-2001 July 17, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Nonprofit Fall 1999 Courses and Evaluations from Scholarship Recipients, 1999 September 9-2000 March 20 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Financial Management, 1999 September 10-20, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Roster with Continuing Education Units, 1999 September-2002 July 18, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Am I Liable?: Responsibilities and Liabilities of Texas Nonprofit Organization Directors, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Completed Certificates, 2000 May 4-2005 April 28, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Collaborative Workshop, 2000 November 6-2001 April 26, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Nonprofit Leadership Retreat, 2000 November 20-2002 April 15, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Heart of Texas Nonprofit Institute 2002, 2002 June 21-August 8, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Heart of Texas Nonprofit Institute 2003, 2002 October 16-2004 January 7 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Heart of Texas Nonprofit Institute 2004, 2004 June 21-2005 January 25 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Nonprofit Leadership Seminar September 18-19, 2003, 2003 July 15-September 19, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Course Catalogs, 1979-2005; 3
  Series III, Course Catalogues, contains the catalogs advertising Continuing Educations course offerings for each semester. The series is in good condition.
  - Catalogs Fall 1981-Winter/Spring 1994 (1 of 4), 1979 Fall-1983 Spring (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Catalogs Fall 1981-Winter/Spring 1994 (2 of 4), 1984 Fall-1989 Fall (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Catalogs Fall 1981-Winter/Spring 1994 (3 of 4), 1989 Fall-1991 Spring (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Catalogs Fall 1981-Winter/Spring 1994 (4 of 4), 1991 Fall-1993 Spring (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs Fall 1993-Winter/Spring 1998 (1 of 2), 1993 Fall-1996 Spring (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Catalogs Fall 1993-Winter/Spring 1998 (2 of 2), 1996 Fall-1998 Spring (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Catalogs Fall 1998-Fall 2002, 1998 Fall-2005 May 13 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Catalogues Winter/Spring 2002-Winter/Spring 2005, 2003 January-2005 May 13 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Catalogs 1990-2005 (1 of 8), 1990 Fall-1993 Spring (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Catalogs 1990-2005 (2 of 8), 1993 Fall-1998 Spring (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Catalogs 1990-2005 (3 of 8), 1995 Spring-1999 Spring (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Catalogs 1990-2005 (4 of 8), 1998 Fall-2001 Spring (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Catalogs 1990-2005 (5 of 8), 2002 Spring-2005 May 13 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Catalogs 1990-2005 (6 of 8), 2003 Fall-2005 Spring (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Catalogs 1990-2005 (7 of 8), 1981 Spring-1989 Fall (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Catalogs 1990-2005 (8 of 8), 1984 Fall-1990 Spring (Box 14, Folder 16)